[Music]
sunshine
i drink water first thing
get coffee and then see if there is an
error on the server
of our website then urgent emails and
then
relax for a bit
[Music]
gosh
this takes too long to smell i am
[Music]
we are walking the door
finish walking the dog go to helichang
and then get the work started for the
day
[Music]
all right that's it for the gym now it's
time to take a shower
because i stink and then i'll just get
work started so that's it
naji is over here
nougat was so
[Music]
so shower finished now one more coffee
and planning i usually do planning
before i start the day
so here as you can see are all the tasks
that i have
to complete i usually do it per week now
i just do it per week
and yeah i just fill up the whole page
and i just cross what i have to do and
today
i already know exactly what i need to do
i need to do these things
right here so that's what i'm going to
be doing i always plan before i even
touch the computer because that helps me
focus
and not waste my time so that's it let's
get started with our work day
12 30 12 30 work starts
[Music]
this is number three coffee cup three
i'm waiting for 6 p.m so i can have my
dinner there's progress going on today
this crust now also this
is crushed
three more tasks and then i attack this
one
so what i want you to try is just just
try to translate this
like this
[Music]
bulgogi this is
what i'm going to eat today and this is
what i'm going to eat
while this food is cooking
[Music]
is
almost 11 pm my meal time is at 6 p.m i
only eat once a day and i eat big
and for one hour and then i don't need
any more it's better
i save time and i just like it more now
that's it i ate a little bit of a break
i'm gonna waste some time
on my phone and then i'm gonna go back
to work until i finish my list
for the day
[Music]
you
you want me to take gear for a walk the
work day is finished
finally
now let's walk the dog and done
[Music]
that's it for this video is late it's
already almost 12 i'm tired
but i'm happy i finished work i went to
the gym i felt productive today
it's not always like this sometimes i
don't accomplish many things but
today i'm happy i did
good night
you